(Bernadette:)I love you, too. If I don't talk
to you before you go to sleep,
(Bernadette:)-I'll meet you in dreamland.
-Good night.
(Amy:)No, I will not consider sleeping
in my garment bag.
(Sheldon:)Penny, did you ever wonder
how Starfleet captains--
(Scene:)No.
(Sheldon:)Well, now that
I've piqued your interest,
(Sheldon:)welcome to the exciting world
of 3D chess.
(Penny:)Why don't you just admit
you only want to play this game
(Penny:)because you always play it
with Leonard and you miss him?
(Sheldon:)You overestimate
his significance in my life.
(Sheldon:)Hm...
(Sheldon:)Do I miss how he makes a face
on my toaster waffle with syrup?
(Scene:)No.
(Sheldon:)Do I miss the way he fixes the zipper
on my jacket when it gets stuck?
(Sheldon:)I don't think so.
(Sheldon:)Do I miss how we say good night
to each other
(Sheldon:)through the walls of our bedroom
using Morse Code?